# Teisha morae

qa lead. trouble shooter. problem solver.

### OVERVIEW

As a Content & Customer Service Specialist for a startup, I've had the opportunity to wear many hats. Aside from my core functions on the Operations team, I've worked with our Product department as a QA lead. In this role, I've improved our QA processes and facilitated tech releases.



919.610.2870



mcraeteisha@gmail.com



600 Willard St. Unit 869 Durham, NC 27701

### EDUCATION

## UNC-CH CODING BOOTCAMP FULL STACK

UNC-CH | CHAPEL HILL, NC JAN. 2021 - JUL. 2021

# BACHELORS DEGREE IN ENGLISH & COMMUNICATION STUDIES

UNC-CH | CHAPEL HILL, NC 2011 - 2015

#### SKILLS

HTML & CSS

**JAVASCRIPT** 

EMAIL MARKETING

**CUSTOMER SERVICE** 

WORDPRESS

ADOBE PHOTOSHOP

FIGMA

**OA TESTING** 

JIRA

MAILCHIMP & SAILTHRU

### WORK EXPERIENCE

AUG. 2017 - PRESENT • CONTENT & CS SPECIALIST, QA LEAD WRITTEN WORD MEDIA | DURHAM, NC

- Audit, improve, and manage the QA Testing Process, optimizing the QA workflow for the team.
- Coordinate QA Testing in preparation for Tech Releases.
- Write company Release Notes, breaking down technical concepts for team members in a digestible format
- The first person on our team, other than our COO, to lead a Tech Release.
- Edit HTML/CSS of 50+ email templates to boost reader engagement
- Create product mockups for new system features
- Daily email creation and customer service

### AUG. 2016 - AUG. 2017 • SOCIAL MEDIA & MARKETING COORDINATOR

MCMILLAN DESIGN / IDS ARCHITECTURE, PA | WAKE FOREST.NC

- Created two company websites with WordPress and kept them up-to-date.
- Designed promotional materials including business cards, advertisements, social graphics, etc.
- Increased brand awareness and boosted company sales by working with the team on all areas of marketing, branding, and company organization.
- Strategically created, curated, and distributed content across the company's social media platforms.